Pedro Santos Skilled front-end developer

Manila, Philippines • devsenioro312@gmail.com

SUMMARY

This is Pedro Santos who is specialized in frontend development with 5 years of experience.

Throughout my frontend development career, I have gained rich and valuable experience and skills in a lot of frontend technological fields such as HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Angular, Vue.

MY AVAILABILITY AS A FRONTEND DEVELOPER

- building responsive and user-friendly user interface.
- restful and third-party api integration.
- always trying to build web solutions that generate growth-driven results for business.
- strict adherence to deadlines is my rule

Plus, you can rest assured that you will get more than expected when hiring me.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Executech Salt Lake City Managed IT Services Company Utah, US

ANGULAR FRONT END DEVELOPER

2022.12-2023.6

- This is the Website that I have worked (https://healthcare.utah.edu/).
- I have worked on Angular 15 project, my role was building new components UI and add funtionalities.
- This website is managed by University of Utah health and it supports hospital functionalities.
- Well-used Components development and npm private module deployment.
- Third-party API and build-in API on the backend integration.
- Used technologies are Angular 15, Rxjs, Directive composition API, Functional router guards

Wealthsimple Inc, CA

REACT FRONT END DEVELOPER

2021.6-2022.6

- Here is the Website that I have worked on (https://www.wealthsimple.com).
- Used technologies are React/Gatsby/Tailwind CSS/Typescript. **Static Site generator built by Gatsby
- This website is being trusted by over 3 million Canadians now.
- Gatsby Static Site generation development by using React for over 1 year

Keysight Technologies, US

VUE FRONT END DEVELOPER

2020.4-2021.4

- Here is the Website that I have worked on (https://cuehealth.com)
- Used technologies are Vue.js/Tailwind CSS
- Cue's molecular COVID-19 test combines fast results and ease of use with the accuracy of central lab technology, all in one device that fits in the palm of your hand.
- Working as a frontend developer with project manager, designer, backend developer

EDUCATION

TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY OF THE PHILIPPINES Bachelor's degree of computer science

MANILA, PHILIPPINES

2016-2020

SKILLS

React • Angular • Vue • Next.js • Next.js • React Hooks • TypeScript • RESTful API • SASS • Tailwind CSS • Bootstrap • HTML • CSS

LANGUAGE

English: Fluent